ALI PAJAND

Montreal, Quebec/Canada • ali.pajand@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/alipajand/ @ alipajand.com/en

Senior Frontend Developer

Summary

I'm an extroverted, energetic, highly positive and hardworking developer with +8 years of expertises in web development (**react** and **vue**) with a history of graphics knowledge.

My main affection is to learn about web and new technologies from various sources of people. I enjoy encountering challenges for which my problem solving ability manifests and expands. I love to see beautiful codes that have an adherence to standards and open-source solutions. I try to figure out all possible solutions but then act based on best practices and standard ways.

To find out more, visit my **Linkedin** account.

Work Experiences

Jul 2021 - Present Senior Frontend Developer (Oslo, Norway)

Birdflocks

Implement website and admin panel with react / next

Feb 2018 - Dec 2021 Senior Frontend Developer (Remote)

CtrlTech

- Tarafdari, Advva, Mapino, Tazebar, Ctrltech, Admartiz, Banikar, Techtoman, Bidzila, FirouzehPlat
- Implement websites, dashboards and admin panels for different startups in vue and react
- SSR version of some applications were in nuxt and next js
- Pwa version or react native apps
- Online chatting with FCM (Firebase)
- Segmenting and drawing on google maps / openstreetmap
- Working with sockets like socket.io or firebase
- Custom service workers and Offline mode for apps
- BDD and TDD tests

Jan 2014 - Dec 2017 Frontend Developer

Rayvarz Software Engineering

- Working in BPMS team (business process management system to rewrite online admin panel and portal in vue)
- Mentoring, UI Discussion and preparing prototypes for programmers
- Collaborate on service catalogue for Ministry of Economic Affairs of Iran
- Change user interface of eOffice to create new sense and change admin panel arguments and texts
- Maintain the old eOffice services and add new feature
- Start to implement new version of company website

Remote Experiences

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021 Senior Frontend Developer (San Francisco, US)

Galliot

Rewrite website and its admin panel with nuxt / vue

May 2020 - Dec 2020 Senior Frontend Developer (Dubai, UAE)

Jeanwest

Implement shop store panel with nuxt / vue

Jan 2020 - May 2020 Senior Frontend Developer (Tehran, Iran)

Deltaban / 3Click

Impletent main website in nuxt and vue frameworks

Apr 2019 - Jul 2019 Frontend Developer (Vancouver, Canada)

Timely

Help to develop and maintain the global application in angular

Jan 2015 - Jan 2017 Frontend Developer (Lahti, Finland)

Lahtiprecision

Implementing three generation of website in these years

Education

Sep 2014 - Aug 2018 M.Sc. Computer/Information Technology Administration

Allame Tabataba'i University

Thesis: Identification of Factors to Use Cloud Computing by University Students in Educational

Process

Sep 2010 - Aug 2014 B.Sc. Engineering/Industrial Management

Allame Tabataba'i University

Skills

Vue js Nuxt js Pure version and Nuxt as ssr framework Vuex as State management tools Familiar with Typescript	React js Next js Gatsby Pure version and Next as ssr framework Redux as State management tools Familiar with Typescript
With Typescript	BDD and TDD tests with Jest , Mocha and E2E
Notifications and Service Workers	Chrome Extension
Onesignal & Google Firebase	Write some extensions for chrome browser
Progressive Web Apps (PWA)	Version Controller
Workbox	Git, SVN and TFS

Created with **TisualCV**